[
    {
        "id":0,
        "question":"What is the allowable cargo load of the LUH-72A in its normal configuration when used for MEDEVAC operations?",
        "answer":"2 litter, 1 medic, and 5 ambulatory."
    },
    {
        
        "id":1,
        "question":"What is the primary use for the CH-47 when used during CASEVAC missions?",
        "answer":"Mass Casualty Evacuation."
    },
    {
        
        "id":2,
        "question":"What is the crew of a LUH- 72A when not being used for MEDEVAC operations?",
        "answer":"(4)Pilot, Co Pilot, Crew Chief, and In-Flight Medic."
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question":"What is the total length of the high performance utility hoist?",
        "answer":"256 feet."
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question":"When used for CASEVAC operations, what is the (ACL) for the CH-47?",
        "answer":"31 ambulatory and 24 litter."
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question":"If the obstacle on the approach route is eight meters tall and the obstacle on the departure route is ten meters tall of your PZ/LZ, what is the unusable space for the departure route?",
        "answer":"100m."
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question":"What reference material covers LZ and/or PZ operations?",
        "answer":"FM 3-21.38."
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question":"What are the dimensions of the reference lights that mark an additional touchpoint for cargo aircraft?",
        "answer":"10mx10m."
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question":"What is the first step in HLZ setup (LZ/PZ Operations)?",
        "answer":"Establish control facilities."
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question":"What size landing point is required for a CH-47 with a long line sling load during nighttime operations?",
        "answer":"Size 7"
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "question":"Why must your sleeves be rolled down when working around aircraft?",
        "answer":"Protect from flying debris & flash fires."
    },
    {
        "id":11,
        "question":"What reference material covers Aircraft Safety?",
        "answer":"FM 3-99"
    },
    {
        "id":12,
        "question":"In the acronym DROP, what does the R stand for?",
        "answer":"Reduce Unnecessary Gear"
    },
    {
        "id":13,
        "question":"What are the three portions of the aircraft that you must avoid at all times?",
        "answer":"Main rotor blade, tail rotor blade, and cargo hook (static electricity)."
    },
    {
        "id":14,
        "question":"In case of a fire, when should you exit the aircraft?",
        "answer":"Immediately."
    },
    {
        "id":15,
        "question":"Define an Air Assault Operation?",
        "answer":"Movement of friendly assault forces by rotary wing aircraft to engage enemy forces or to seize and hold key terrain."
    },
    {
        "id":16,
        "question":"What is a chalk/load defined as?",
        "answer":"Personnel and equipment designated to be moved by a specific aircraft."
    },
    {
        "id":17,
        "question":"What are the six factors that determine abort criteria?",
        "answer":"Weather, time, available aircraft, mission essential combat power, mission criticality, and enemy."
    },
    {
        "id":18,
        "question":"What are the components of an Air Route?",
        "answer":"SP, RP, ACP, and flight path."
    },
    {
        "id":19,
        "question":"What are the three terrain flight modes?",
        "answer":"Low level, contour, and NAP of the Earth."
    },
    {
        "id":20,
        "question":"What reference material covers Aircraft Orientation?",
        "answer":"FM 3-04."
    },
    {
        
        "id":21,
        "question":"What is the cruise speed of the AH-6J/MH-6J?",
        "answer":"135 knots."
      
    }
]
